<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CEO Dictionary</string>
    <string name="jobs1">Steve Jobs</string>
    <string name="musk1">Elon Musk</string>
    <string name="prichai1">Sundal Pichai</string>
    <string name="billy1">Bill Gates</string>
    <string name="parker1">Mark Parker</string>
    <string name="coock1">Tim Cook</string>
    <string name="waren1">Warren Buffett</string>
    <string name="pichai">One another, which was born in 1972 in Tamil Nadu, India (Tamil Nadu) State, was brought up in Chennai Province. His father was an electrician. Family of Blood differences were not so generous side. Most of the talk about the IT industry is that the founder or CEO faces have an interesting childhood computer, but here it is one another exception. He did not try also visited the computer before going to college. Instead, it was given to avoid differences genius memorization. He could memorize a phone number where a recent contact with a contact of the bystanders. His parents have noticed blood on the memorization of these differences were not in spite neokneokji Salim and decided to send the blood differences in college. One another with the help of parents it could be admitted to the Darfur (Kharagpur) Campus Kara Indian Institute of Technology (Indian Institute of Technology). He studied metallurgical engineering was selected independent of the computer. Considered in the Indian hand in the industrial city of Kanpur was the most popular color that major recipients. However, admission to one another, one university, which will meet the machine to change his life. Was the computer. Facing one another, the computer and software industry began to grow rapidly in the early 1990s it became a great interest in computer science not as good as his major. He was self-taught, so as to create a chess program immersed in computer engineering. This one another, a 1993 graduate from college with honors, was selected as a scholarship student at Stanford University. The received more scholarships than a year annual salary of one another, which his father went to the US to study road. After completing a master\'s degree in materials engineering at Stanford University made the decision to get a job in corporate America. His first job was Applied Materials makes semiconductor production equipment (Applied Materials). He lived a life as an engineer after completing a Master\'s (MBA) in Business Administration from the University of Pennsylvania School Watson decided to live a life as a corporate administrator. 2002 graduate of the school, and while Watson goes for semiconductor-related consulting at McKinsey Consulting Group joined Google in 2004.</string>
    <string name="jobs">I think that \"going to die is a big help whenever an important choice in life. Because almost all of the people, including expectations, all pride, all fear of failure things become meaningless in the face of death remain a very important thing. If you remember that death can avoid the trap of thinking that to lose something. You eopeuni lose no reason not to follow your heart. \" - Steve Jobs\' commencement speech at Stanford University in 2005, Steve Jobs was born in San Francisco, California, USA, 1955. I opposed the conservative Americans for being married mother Joanne Simpson family house was the biological father of Abdul Fatah John cup Syrian otherwise, Joanne Simpson eventually chose to adopt after the birth of Jobs with status of single mothers. The Simpsons has won a couple of highly educated college graduates to the new parents of Jobs. And it was actually going to be a lawyer and his wife adopted a Jobs. But they chose instead to Jobs girls at the last moment, Jobs went to Paul and Clara Jobs Jobs couple, who were on a waiting list. Simpson Paul Jobs did not graduate and even high school Clara Jobs had refused to sign the final adoption papers due to the fact that did not graduate from college, \"I just go to college, Steve\" to the Jobs couple is allowed to come off until the adoption under the promise did. Northern California at the time were placed at the crossroads of rapid change. On the one hand, technology has developed rapidly, and the rage that psychedelic music and mysticism passed the other hand, in the United Kingdom. Both cultures had a major impact on jobs. Jobs was a fan of the Beatles and adherents of liberalism. This can be understood only look black turtleneck and jeans outfit that it can be said of Jobs\' trademark. After graduating from high school, Jobs was admitted to study medicine and literature in the Reed College (Reed College) in Portland, Oregon. But Reed College tuition could attend only one semester too expensive to blame. Even to sleep on the floor in friends\' meals to resolve the Coke bottle into a plate of money and free meals living, he did not put the strap of learning through the audit. Especially when he heard calligraphy class was also later exert a great influence on the Macintosh fonts. A few years later, Jobs returned to California and joined the Homebrew Computer Club with Wozniak (Homebrew Computer Club). To find the one that he really liked. Soon after working with Wozniak founded Apple in Jobs\' parent\'s garage and came up with the \'Apple I\', the first personal computer. After the sequel \"Apple Ⅱ \'it is as reap the unexpected success of the Jobs and Apple seemed to be winning. But experienced a slump after a few times to release of Apple\'s board of directors, Jobs, 30 years old, fired him. Jobs fell in a few months panic was founded NeXT again acquired Pixar, and was it a foothold in the recovered (after Pixar pulled created \"Toy Story\" Considered as the most successful animation in the world, was acquired by Disney from George Lucas 1000 Pixar was acquired only dollars can be called truly great success\'ve sold it to Disney for $ 7.4 billion). Same time, Lauren Powell became the lover is married in 1991. Between Jobs and Powell had a daughter named Lisa, born between the two, but the children of the first sons and two daughters, Jobs in fact long ago I had a girlfriend yet. But Jobs did not recognize Lisa\'s daughter. It was because he thought that he was sterile. Thus support is also not sent properly. Jobs later I realized that he was the father of Lisa, had even put her name on the new computer as a means of sorry. This is just the first mouse-driven computer \"Lisa computer. In 1996, Apple bought NeXT. And Jobs has returned as CEO of Apple. After returning, he created a myth that switching to a surplus of $ 400 million in one year alone a deficit of $ 1 billion in 1997. He released products iMac, iPod, iPhone, iPad, etc. succeeded in a row, Apple is olraseoge tall as the best IT companies in the world. But the illness came along with business success. Jobs received a pancreatic cancer diagnosis in 2004 had a major surgery. In 2009, also received a liver transplant surgery. Gradually deteriorating health doeja stepped from the end position Chief Executive Officer in 2011, and left the old world in the same year on October 5th 56 years.</string>
    <string name="billy">Of American businessmen, donate Foundation, programmer and developer of the world\'s PC operating system, Microsoft Windows, Microsoft founder\'s ball, which occupied 76.52% of the market. Also went and dropped out of Harvard University sseonaeryeo a success story in MS-DOS and Windows, 80 ~ 90\'s, was popular enough to be the first thing that comes when the IT industry figures. From 1995 to 2017 the figures, which accounted for more than 20 years rich world # 1 ranking. It has been maintained for a very long time the sign digit of the world\'s first, thanks to the owner of the spring does not dry out, the 2017 was naejueo seat to descend on the Amazon, Jeff Bezos, chairman of the world richest 1. He was often described as a target of such people fear to fly back to the Empire, even if only if the incumbent wealth, lord of darkness, the world is changing all the negative images that between an unprecedented philanthropy after retiring. Worldwide and operates in the most overwhelmingly large charitable foundation, children have been the subject also declared Giving inherited only less than 0.1% of your property. And also appealed to participate in donations from around the world signed, to persuade campaign was largely agents around the world. Now it is revered as a symbol of code to practice a donation. He actually referred to as a schoolboy style without passing through the solid angular in society. But a young man has the face of ambitious enough to drop out of Harvard University and bare hands into the computer business. In the days of suffering and in full haeteotdago even think, \"Should I just doctors.\" But would one describe under the look of the actual move has secretly rebellious temperament. It caught committing a DUI when the police college. And writes that the competitor\'s products to computer manufacturers stories that would not threaten the delivery of Windows, but these yiraeseon necessarily because legally it is a problem, it measures bokdolyi president and \"prohibit the release of the free OS PC\". But he was also the one to put handageona \"You have to make the case that what the program is free, but you must not invade the area of ​​MS\", secretly put the code that competing products will not work properly in OS. In fact, this degree it is true tolerable Although a lot of big companies, but anyway, saying that this man is honest and wealth but clearly does not fit. # No more demons (Demon of Silicon valley) of the \"Silicon Valley was once nicknamed the \"boasted unscrupulous business was a resourceful enough. Handing over the chief executive officer (CEO) Steve Ballmer place in 2000 receded to 2 lines. Since with the new president took the chief software architect (Chief Software Architect) position. While handing over the chief software architect (CSA) Ray Ozzie to the position in 2006 was in fact he launched a retirement job. As of June 27, 2008, he retired from the Microsoft chairman. This ttetda as a whole hand in the management of Microsoft. The chairman of the board but that is retained. That is not the president batjiman salary would continue the story a whole bunch of bees on Microsoft thanks. Until 2007 was the world\'s richest person with a fortune of $ 600. But recently he received the \"world\'s richest\" title of Bill Gates threatened by changes in stock value. To Mexican telecommunications tycoon Carlos Slim of handing over the title \"world\'s richest\" himself seemed to remain as \"America\'s Best Rich\". However, starting from May 2013 billionaires in the world rankings are calculated from Bloomberg ahead of Carlos Slim was crowned No. 1 again. Continue in that eopchirak dwichirak while the later was dropped back to second place in the Forbes top one nyeonen again crowned 2015. In November 2017 the current was crowned Jeff Bezos of Amazon.com, the world\'s richest tycoon. Anyway bakkwieodo continues to rank named Bill Gates is the richest man leading a pronoun. It grew up comfortably in a wealthy family. My father was a prominent lawyer who runs the best law firm in Seattle mother was a member of the board of directors of First Interstate Bank of America bank system and non-profit organizations the United Way. Then ride the Phenom temperament, was recognized as an early genius either completely memorize the Cathedral, Father Sermon on the Mount in the Bible puts in a condition to take to the fair (in Matthew Chapter 5 is more appropriate in Chapter 7) shows the mathematically gifted. See his IQ is very high as 160. Also it was a huge bookworm. Do not put the book in the table and the parents always namuratda. Gifted genius was always at school with honors and he quickly learned the management and programming. Naetneunde appear to prominence on the computer from when I was in the Lakeside School, one day, to hack into the central computer, which was connected with Paul Allen School terminals, that even a ridiculous thing erased from debt accounting books the school had been. Note that Paul Allen and Gates\' friend, is also a partner when regains Microsoft. How then pass the crisis, and that was the entrance to Harvard Law, mainly the law rather than subjects taking a forerunner of Applied Mathematics (applied math) courses in computer science. Yet, gather like-minded friends to say a thing or a bad man, or program development. He wrote a thesis on algorithms that time carried on discrete mathematics journals. Information that presents an algorithm for the problem of Pancakes # sorting, better algorithms emerged only after 30 years. Often when you are young businessman in the IT field for much the word gates of the second, there are few cases achieved academic achievements, like Gates of them. Go to graduate school if there are many people who can not write a doctoral thesis as an important papers gates. If you receive a doctorate degree course but gained another research achievement. Software companies of the Harvard school days and that Heneywell\'ve worked with Paul Allen friend. Seen briefly worked as a summer handeut while working as a summer intern. Eventually he dropped out of Harvard to Microsoft\'s business. Later, dude was an honorary diploma from Harvard University. People thought he had a leave of absence to know that so ambitious fact that he dropped out of business eventually released, not to return to school at the time. Then it several years later, was when you first launch the PC from IBM Corporation. Microsoft has contracts to supply the operating system for the PC to IBM. So the rights and source code of Seattle Computer Q-DOS, and to recruit the originator and developer teams Patterson of Q-DOS name also earned a fortune by selling back changed to MS-DOS. Whatever agreement he signed with IBM, called the agreement kkichin most affected computer in history. Eventually, IBM Manda money to be a MS peojun font. After the catch is fully in control of the OS market with Windows series. IBM-PC operating agreement with IBM also were very lucky to follow, but the first place you want to deal in IBM, MS, MS at the time did not have its own operating system. So Gates was introduced to Gary Kildall of Digital Research go from making a lot of the time sseuyideon CP / M. But the end is why do not care for each contract with IBM talks were broken off. The intervention Gates said something once again, on both sides, and when Digital Research did not very actively contract was broken off. So the contract was worried Basic MS is not sold out was made by IBM, the PC market is not worried lest the PC slow. The Gary Kildall right charyeoteumyeon spirit MS would not have been without success as it is now. Kjeldahl MS-DOS, MS-DOS discussed aware that the company\'s CP / M-86 and the appearance or technical and very similar to its operating system also made official by threatening the operating system IBM. So IBM PC has been sold while the operating system is not included, the operating system was purchased to choose freely in the market. But Digital Research sold the enormous price of a whopping $ 240 remaining confidence the technical excellence of the CP / M-86. While the MS-DOS was sold for about $ 40. After CP / M-86 was soon fell networks. Later, the spirit charyeoseo DR-DOS, but also come up even after the market was already fully crossed for MS. And already it is being also go to the window. Eventually Digital Research was gradually destroyed, and they are shown a series of goof on the PC is still talked about earlier. However Kjeldahl\'s assessment of a very different story, and to the claims that the story above is not true, and the Kjeldahl that hate Bill Gates Bill Gates in his autobiography is \"He is divisive. He is manipulative. He is a user . He has taken much from me and the industry. \" Originally equipped with the world\'s first GUI computer is a Xerox Star (Xerox Star) born in 1981. Here the famous Xerox Xerox is right as a copier manufacturer. The PARC was their tablet PC, e-mail, dozens of times using the internal network to go ahead in technology! Apple\'s Steve Jobs received a great impression on the Xerox Star GUI system could be to scout the PARC team novelties not recognized within the company created the first commercial GUI mode PC \"Apple Lisa (Lisa)\" of the world in 1984. In particular, while financial pressures as against Apple after Jobs\' exit naeteotda made a lot of anecdotal ruthless business as Devil\'s Silicon Valley. Microsoft will receive a GUI patent license to Apple succeeded in Windows 1.0 sikyeotgo born in 1985 and extends the maturity method computing GUI separately around the world. Bill Gates is one to two years to become obsolete not used skillfully (Apple 2) Apple software renewal was possible in groups naeteot obtained in November 1985 for a permanent license for the Macintosh user interface from John Sculley. Not exactly Microsoft, Apple received a license for the GUI for software development using the fact that the expiration date of the license is not written gall to bring mandeuneunge the OS of Microsoft. But Apple\'s side insisted that the corresponding license is a one-time, Microsoft argued that taking over a permanent license expiration date has not been written. For this reason, Apple, Microsoft, but to make a copyright lawsuit in 1988, the judge issued a ruling that Apple passed the \"reckless\" to the user interface to Microsoft in 1985, permanently. In addition, Apple has purchased a license for the technology for the GUI and the GUI from Xerox, had a patent for a GUI element that they have direct development. And talk based on this to Microsoft\'s lawsuit against the GUI piracy, Bill Gates to ask for help from Xerox, lawyers will find a GUI source patent with Xerox (Until then, Xerox executives they have a GUI source patents The unaware itneunjido). Eventually Apple\'s unique GUI patent also two days is deemed made on the source of lost patent Xerox GUI GUI to invalidate Apple\'s patents. In addition, the Mac is something you\'ve buried Basic. Let\'s know what this was being Don demonstration of Apple\'s development of Mac Basic superior BASIC interpreter being built in microphone Microsoft, hagoseon needs to abandon the Mac BASIC as an excuse to Apple\'s software contracts, buying a mac Basic a $ 1 was indefinitely suspended following sources: It is something you\'ve discarded by the total amount of code and copy. As you can see above figures also outstanding talent as a programmer, but above all it is over, very good talent as a businessman also counted as the cause of success. In fact, many cases of MS are somehow screwed competitors jeojilreoseo the shoveling … . It is very important to make fewer mistakes. Original War is not the winning side well prepared to fight to win this page to make fewer mistakes. In fact, the greatest achievements of Bill Gates goes beyond the above achievements would have made it so that the software (= pure digital content, do not get caught in the hand) it may be sold by itself or such a paradigm. Bill Gates would come forward until paid to sell their software, all software was able to create added value only as part of a comprehensive computing services combined with the type or hardware. That is copyright to the powers of intangible Code in the United States until the previous bundle itself would not have thought to buy goods to sell. Then it may say that makes Bill Gates may exist countless current commercial software company in the world thanks to assert exclusive property rights to the software and establish a business model for its sale. It appreciated China is part look compared to Apple. Apple just sold with its combination of software and hardware today. This can be called (In a sense, the older generation) of the same business model as IBM\'s era did it before any other Unix-based companies did. From beyond this older generation business model ever built a new model to sell products to independent software, namely intangible digital content in itself is just like a Bill Gates.</string>
    <string name="musk"><![CDATA[The American CEO. It was founded with the online payment services company predecessor x.com, rocket manufacturing company president and private space company Space X PayPal, which also serves the CEO of electric car company Tesla. Current job title is CEO, the CEO of Tesla and Space X, is responsible also chairman of Solar City. It is famous for its future oriented company. Current is also actively invest in promising industries and SMEs. In particular, support was also $ 700 million to Ai non profit organization, there is a big interest in developing safe artificial intelligence. Among the biggest threats to contemporary humanity has known the message he left has said it would be artificial intelligence. If you want to know more about it by reading a good translation, published in nylon Maersk Gimm Young Publishers. Maersk person, as well as a well written detail on the basis of the electric interviews with various people around. The high recognition and popularity among corporate CEO to travelogue and innovative moves. Just as Steve Jobs can discuss Apple"s cash, except for nylon Maersk can not talk about the Tesla and Space X. In South Africa, Pretoria, 1971 was born in engineer father and model mother. Ever since I got interested in computer programming languages ​​to learn on his own, when 12 year old created a game called Blastar  along with his brother and sold it for $ 500 in gaming magazines ($ 1,200 in current value). Childhood was known as a bookworm reading 10 hours a day, and that particularly fascinated with fantasy and science fiction. I mentioned euron was Lord of the Rings books and favorite guide to the Galaxy The Hitchhiker did. In addition, there is also a hobby making model rocket that will never put a test launch that used to make rocket fuel mixture of gasoline and various chemicals on a birch rocket. Handeda original body weak and others are the basic thing to being bullied by kids around you see a different and unique moves and had been harassed by the violence associated. Musk was divorced parents age who was still a student of the Maersk, Maersk and the rest of the brothers were both entrusted to his father, Errol musk. Father Errol is currently living in South Africa mother being served as the model still active even in old age. Please note, nylon Musk is a very bad between the mother and only get along well even now affectionately father, Errol. He mentioned several times about the wounds had been forced to put his father in his autobiography many have complained about the father of his brother down, as well as the eldest son of nylon. In a recent interview even my father is the devil and horrible yellow dog. This is a person who committed all the atrocities and crimes that you can imagine. He was talking to peongpeong crying during the interview. The Errol between the rich, such as attacking a son called back a little example of iron seemed completely twisted. However, only the nylon IMHO … Thats also the father of a very ardent human mattana son said. I have had enough children to and from the magnetic stepdaughter. Note that the current age of the man is 72 years old and chinmo former wife and stepdaughter of this is currently divorced his daughter was one of Oregon"s daughter was married magnetic jeokeneun from the age of four grew well. Since Maersk last time the youth is samneunda goal to make the "90s ended the Cold War, to think that moving to the US to study center and settle in the United States. In addition, at the time South Africa was being enforced conscription, enlistment was also musk person who was South African nationals. Musk and did not want to do military service. Fortunately, with the help of the mother was Canadian citizen could acquire the citizenship of Canada. Canada is so easy to get a green card or US citizenship a person manyirado can get Canadian citizenship at birth if the civil party, foresight and geographic and cultural proximity to the United States during the parent Musk immediately determine the Canadian line. Two years it studied physics at Queen"s University in Ontario, the United States transfer to the University of Pennsylvania, physics and economics at the Open University of Pennsylvania completed in Wharton better stayed one year after the completion of a credit for taking Physics for 2 years Economics Credits 2 for one concludes with a bachelor majors. This was also briefly worked in the midst of game companies to work part time. But later he admitted to materials science at Stanford University in 1995 to complete a PhD, and dropped out of school in two days, while decided to lift the road of entrepreneurship. But we walked down the highroad and founded several companies, was in reality a lot of tremendous suffering. In particular was the 2000s, mid to late is the largest ferns, the bitterness that ate a lot of swearing when with the problem row in the battery and transmission occurs mirwojyeot Our official Tesla Roadster chailpiil, failed both because the rocket launch experiments in space X suntanchi to third saw. Of course, he came out on the dock enormous bottomless money ridiculously out of water swelling, went up just before the nylon bag is empty teongteong manghagi. Fortune eopgedo the global financial crisis was not easy even rolled up money circulation in September 2008. The mid 2010s, the time of humiliation that reigning driven the frame passed the crisis, barely a while Tesla most are short sales amounts in the corporate world until about the situation get out of the sound that the production problems of Tesla Motors grab the ankles bankruptcy within three months of the financial district Feedback was also the. Moreover, as devoted to one style was neglected in the home while the divorce because his wife paid a large annoyed. Nylon time was a total of five children together two twins and triplets. Look at why it is required to divorce a wife for granted. After the divorce proceedings had to finish a large amount of child support, alimony + 1 + Tesla Roadster to his wife for free. Second wife, Lula de Riley and also after a short marriage and divorce, the divorce was final, and then through the separation reunited after a bit of rest. Through two marriages Maersk is the first 4.2 million US dollars (about 46 million) when divorce when divorce was second only to pay alimony of about 16 million US dollars (177 million). The great thing Musk Tesla asset management are dedicated to a lawyer create a sufficient agreement before marriage than divorce risk. He was a kind of experiment to find out how much is needed for you before the foundation. To eat to live and write in ssikman $ 1 a day, and held out for a month with frozen hot dogs and orange. He also determined the experimental results andago so bad to live with a dollar a day, and began start up without hesitation. The goal of the foundation decided to internet, space, green energy "sector. Since each by founding PayPal, Space X, Solar City is successful. It is still the world"s known as a denial of people belonging to less intimate greedy side. Musk but are interested in the original energy business, internet business you are looking at the possibility of development in Silicon Valley, and immediately decided to jump on the internet business. Not started a class at Stanford in 1995, dropped out of school in just two days, the time spent is also called his brother, who studied business administration in Silicon Valley at Queens College, he founded his first company, jiptu Corporation (Zip2 Corporation) at 23 years old. Jiptu was acquired for $ 307 million on media such as The New York Times was a company that provides local information such as maps and information of the company, in February 1999 Compaq. During that time, shares of Maersk was $ 22 million at 7%. 28 years of age will be a millionaire. But jeongjak Compaq reported large losses dotcom bubble turned off and did not do well running a company out of business and the acquisition of the company. Compaq eventually became the seed money that can only count peojun feasting larger project to nylon musk. 1999 passed the nylon Zip2 to Compaq"s established online bank X dot (X.com) with close colleagues trio and use your email address to devise a way to send money. Merger with a company called Community Configurator (Confinity) that was developed for the same service in 2000 and changed its company name to PayPal (Paypal). The two companies are competing with each other was and will continue to progress its strategic merger with two companies, both agree that will destroy all while only competition. As an aside Community Configurator is eotneunde original X com is owned and operated offices being rented while moving the office to change its name to PayPal, became the name of the merged company by name. But got this opinion conflicts with members often happen after a merger, eventually Manda colleagues jjalrigo CEO in the wind to raise haeiman the Board of Directors. But at the time when eBay acquired PayPal for $ 1,500,002,002 years PayPal has approximately 11% equity iteotgie Maersk announces widespread name as a young businessman owns a capital of up to about $ 1.7 billion. After success in internet business with PayPal Musk turned his eyes in the field of energy industry and aerospace industry was interested in since college. In fact, I think the first time to make nylon Musk + Rocket Ship Set between his hands full with the Saturn rocket that can be a little bit cargo sent to the planet Mars V class was very large at all. 2001 At the time, he can turn into space, to the attention of the people to broadcast publicly the growth of plants sent to Mars through the screw mini greenhouse, fill a small plant in the for hydration gels named Mars Oasis again increase the screws budget It was the idea of ​​suggesting so. But after modifying the screws and other consequences of the ticks browsing the data of the space industry, one Businessman me for sticking absolute non value strategy, even technicians switched buy cans ICBM removed the Russian nuclear warheads to go shooting direction Plus the room and through contacts the pull holding collect the cash bags react, to Russia as thin ribbons being handed the box back to. In the plane returning from Russia, he reached the conclusion that it is better motivation I beat the calculator I"m just making it up to shoot a rocket Establish 2002 Space X. Right motivation to make rockets for space travel at an affordable price target for the company. Musk is not that simply running the company as CEO, devoted his life to it. Tesla and Solar City is also a minor project compared to the space X. He poured literally poured their wealth has largely involved in rocket design. Deda is from childhood interest in rockets were many cases this it is a great help studied physics at the university. Early years were laughed at people because of unrealistic ideas rockets because they made need Den tremendous technology and money to shoot artefacts in the universe and stand impossible not funded at national level, and therefore one private company In to rocket production When there was a majority opinion atmospheres why reputedly the finger pointing was granted. In fact, a number of effective liaison engineer to create a Falcon 1 rocket, but the experiment is secured to the boss feet, saw the bitter attempts to launch 1 3 all failed. Rocket scientists, including nylon are sikyeotgo overcome only ppajyeotji the menbung dramatically successful launch in the fourth  Since then scored many successes. This is the first recorded successful satellite launch as a private businessman, not a government agency. Due to this success the space X is the recognition of skills and receive a stable investment and take orders from various countries have raised the rocket successfully launched. NASA also wanted to send a supply ship to the International Space Station (ISS) has been using the space X. There was originally extradited by a rocket spilling away again while writing the first success of the idea of ​​charging only the fuel and re committed in 2015 will receive a huge subsidy of up to about 3 trillion won from Hanwha screws. Lotta people to the mistaken geolro that surplus to reuse the idea of ​​a rocket is figured deficit underway beautifully the nylon Maersk business.  Is somehow the private sector saw clear results did not disclose, in 2014 operating profit to $ 1B sales 0.2 It is estimated to be%. But it will have more small operating profit and net profit margin (net income). 2015 operating profit to $ 0.95B sales rather is a deficit $ 260M (approximately 300 billion won). Engineers Gwynn syotwel current vice president and chief operating officer of Space X (Gwynne Shotwell) This leads to the right arm of nylon. When in the late 2000s as a series of missile tests failed space X wobbly and created the opportunity to win many cases the rocket launch contracts with NASA and several companies escape the crisis. This is because that the nylon and when I interview new employees of the space X to be directly involved flies a lot of difficult questions. Yes, even the haeol headhunting talent from other companies. Up in January 2016 finally brought a plate of Mars Oasis I was initially thought was a bomb in 2025 declared motivation to send people to Mars. At this point it touches the space X of ambition is not just a space industry niche markets. In a speech in September 2016, the International Astronomical Congress held in Mexico on the 27th May announced the "Interplanetary Transport System" of specific proposals. The ITS has been a part of many adjustments to reality in 2019 basically the theme of 100 ton giant Saturn V rocket unsongryang with the size of the level has been maintained without being developed. Before and after the 2010s seems to be announcing that the Department of Defense, as well as space exploration julyigetda Russian military satellite in dependence on the field as part of the Russian sanctions contributed to the launch of a military satellite.  Musk is not surprising that even the Most High, who pulled out of sight of the hearing, the Department of Defense. Rather, the 2014 hearing me in my presence, CEO of ULA blown display of "together, we completely American made at affordable prices in Russia are the guys writing the price of the engine changryeol" was to completely rob the ULA side. The Pentagon, as well as too many NASA officials noted the Falcon Heavy and has also built vigilant competitors such as ULA, Arianespace. Recycling attempt Falcon and Dragon series has already become the subject of benchmarking in the next generation of launch vehicles, spacecraft studies from around the world. To the success of the launch pelkeon Heavy launch on February 6, 2018 it was engraved on the world once again his ability. Another 5 2020 July, the world"s first private manned orbital spacecraft Dragon V2 ship manned even yirueotgo in earnest in late 2018 ten stars prototypes drying started (Space X) since the mid 2019 feat of a successful space flight SSTO and plans to continue to try to test. Satellite Internet is not a star brand was launched in the space X also links into it. We arrange satellites more than 10,000 in the Low Earth Orbit is expected to cover almost all parts of the world. Since the end of 2020 is limited to the start of the Internet service in North America is starting a worldwide service since 2024. When Musk Learn one of the most thought I Tesla company Martin Eberhard and Marc other is penning the electric car company co founded in 2004, nylon Musk has invested heavily based on the Paypal stake was the largest shareholder, Martin Eberhard and mark Pennington is leaving the company to take the other is nylon Maersk CEO has reached so far. It has created a car back to 100% electric motor, not a hybrid. Of the Model S, including the Tesla Roadster to start hitting the jackpot Considered as one of the best electric car manufacturer in the world. And new companies are looked compared to the famous car brand oversized smaller and less popular, a lot, but growing rapidly on the basis of EV and 12 June 2014, CEO nylon Maersk has announced a public all the patents of Tesla Motors through blogs . The title is a parody of the All your base are belong to us. The reason is that in order to foster the electric car market. Because of his extraordinary personality He stipulate that the unique car that challenges the conventional paradigm of automotive companies. It is the SEXY collect car models initials, or a close but look a glance irrational dageona serving them sleek car design. In the spirit of innovative design, interesting presentations, the name change.  comes to mind is Apple. Of course, to look from the point of view of corporate strategy when start ups are common position heunhadi fully along the flow of the market itself has no merit at all in the company. If the war as it is usual hubalju card that dont hold out targeting the niche baen IMHO low price inde When it was first class in the field seemed established strategy. And there"s a jackpot that strategy to overtake Toyota in July 2020 Mon current market cap ranks first among global automotive company. Boasts of a whopping $ 300 billion market cap crazy and S & amp; P 500, including just before the daily situation. Molryeot several times, but the bankruptcy listening to the assessment gyeondyeonaego both the hump and at the same time changed the paradigm geueum a large stroke in the automotive market shares of Tesla are soaring day after day. Musk is also playing a major shareholder wealth lanky. Co founded the company in 2006. In the early days of the solar panel installation haejumyeonseo almost free it has expanded aggressively into the business. It was started as a personal project aims to green energy and cheap energy supply, unlike other electric car companies lost even though there was a good technology and Tesla Motors engineers have a hidden gongsin prevail. In fact, the concept of electric cars has been forgotten in the market, but since I was the car market, quicken confrontation and petrol cars pushed the benefits of gasoline. Later, but be simply a number whenever popping oil shocks forgotten businessmen will challenge the electric car business, was it the majority due to the limitations of battery capacity can not travel the distance is more than even 100km because of problems such as to charge the battery once it takes a few hours the practical beonbeonhi had failed. Musk is a battery related business as it determines the future of electric cars, solar energy is focused through Solar City, which was produced cheaply than the battery electric vehicle to invest, directly or indirectly. In 2014 20% more efficient than the conventional method and the price was reduced by 20% with the batteries in the Tesla plans to sell the vehicle came to a similar price to existing gasoline powered vehicles. In 2016, it became by the lobby of NV Energy owned by Buffett"s Berkshire Hathaway prospects of the company opaque wearing a striking colossal Solar City is a terrific Musk held by the necessary Solar City for electric Tesla GB argument Tesla to keep the factory It was. Since Op greatly increased the negative outlook on the future of Tesla for several years as a matter of course. In addition, the eccentricity What are some of musk? Management of many companies, and shows the degree of eccentricity crazy incredible yiragon people working in all sectors. Especially proficient level (shitposting) writes ppeolgeul via Twitter is a master geupil. See more in the unfolding caught without your great business plan and presentation, and the Internet is not between Famous writings containing the original vision for the future meme pictures or just drips are also very ugly. Once it became a topic for answers that stand up to the brow of the Orient Â kage project Izumi tweets are "different show Bowser 0 shares cosplay "" In fact, I said this is my cat girl Gonzo it. Before that is under I ♡ anime tweet or not to go not this ohdeok such as raising up the hansumswineun or tweet  Bitcoin Moe Tuesday fired the Miku concert that is questionable. Due to the fixed gear tooth ohdeok photos of Kakegawa figure wearing a T shirt guruyi. May 2018 there was a candy that you create a company to win the rich Warren Buffett, the world"s third largest. Buffett will let you attract them to fight back is not true that Maersk break the candy business in which they invest. Buffett vs Maersk "Candy fight" I July 2018, the girlfriend Grimes posted a tweet that the featured what K Pop to his favorite on the new song of the girls in the group two months, where the two months girl without a Famous Comments He posted a tweet that Shara smiling. By starring in Joe Logan Experience "is a live podcast of September 2018 May 7, comedian Joe Logan goes to smoke marijuana blended whiskey was the drink controversy. However, it is picked by attaching directly to the fire"s it"s not a suction draft recommendation by marijuana smoking was the host. It musk also asked if he had inhaled reported to be a legitimate host. And the legalization of marijuana is the place where shares of marijuana in the Western United States alone was enough to cause controversy in the fact that even sokhagin Anna levels vary greatly yirang tobacco and alcohol, a prominent business leaders openly smoked marijuana. Yeotdamyeon Maersk general corporate executive, but one end, so go away, the problem is that the space X which he states that management signed a contract with the US Air Force. According to military regulations that employees deal with the US was in a position to once again be the investigation of this problem, because marijuana smoking is prohibited. And in the end the US Air Force development contract type expendable launch vehicles (Evolved Expendable Launch Vehicle) is available since 2021 instead of a space X was selected Omega rocket Northrop Grumman.  Bloberg has reported that the Pentagon is reviewing the secret of the clearance space X. In February 2019 with Justin roil land Rick and Morty while starring in "Meme Review" video of PewDiePie nwatda upset the hustle and internet. Already olrigin a tweet that suggests, in January, but the time has just made everyone naedureuge tongue again twilji atmospheres do not know where to move the Maersk went over to drip. 31 March 2019 , the sound in the cloud olrimyeo rap about gorillas Haram Entebbe was crowned on SoundCloud wrapper. When someone yieotdamyeon indeda early as April Fools" Day prank but here he wasted no wonak quality it is a man who saw everyone "too Maersk" reactions called. April 2019 has changed the Twitter peusa Edward elrik screenshots without the Famous again switched to the famous picture by the amount "Absolute Unit" meme. June 2019 has changed the profile picture to black deoni raise the tweets" Twitter account was deleted, he changed his nickname to "Daddy DotCom". This was when Twitter (!), Even the Tesla shares in your account to delete posts temporarily skyrocket. Of course, after a few days when a star is geuraetnya as enjoying a coffee, sitting on top roadster hood on Mars  peusa changing the atmosphere again to start writing a ppeolgeul. 8 May, 2019 Aunt Bee has not  US La throwing a tweet immediately following the Teletub then leaned write the Queen  La throwing mud Tweet dressed in the colors of the Teletubbies.  Original tweet also mentions been running a pro all kinds Bee drip down. I posted a tweet made sweets with 8 years May 19, 2019, issue one yen kids had a Kirby shaped cookies are among the odd appearance of the cake, this part of the course, Kirby fans breathed. The figure, which is further invited to watch the game awards held in December 2019 was also caught on camera. Woman beside nylon Musk is yikumi Nakamura (中 村 育 美) gave a strong impression to emerge in the developer, Bethesda last E3 2019 presentation of the game Tango Works. May 2020 May 2, has posted on Twitter equal shares of Tesla"s too high. Naturally Tesla shares was  10 percent plunge, while the market capitalization on the day decreased to 140 billion dollars (17). 5 lighted called his name of birth is Grimes 04 X Æ A 12. Jjaewon? But because I can get a number to the name by California law to modify the name, it just changed the 12 in Roman numbers X Æ A Xii. In the words of my nylon Musk pronounced X Ash Day Twelve. According to Grimes Description X is unknown (unknown variable), Æ is AI Elf way of spelling (AI + "love" in Chinese / Japanese), (...), and A Xii was the predecessor of the SR 71 it means that the tester a 12. Twitter without the Famous Pyramids of Egypt at the end of July 2020 clearly it responded to look out came the reply directly to the Egyptian Party Egyptian Minister of International Cooperation and the aliens did.]]></string>
    <string name="parker">Mark Parker is a graduate of the University of Pennsylvania political science and joined Nike as a sneaker designer in 1979. He "Running enthusiasts' activities in high school athletes. Unlike the major reason for the company to enter the shoes. CEO Parker was evaluated as excellent business sense designers both in and out of the company. Since joining undergone various departments such as design, product development, marketing, new business sectors in China. 1998 nyeonen through the global sneaker sector unit general manager, Nike co-president in 2001 was appointed CEO in 2006. He is right after the CEO position has been steadily involved in the sneaker design. Nike's design team is called the 'HTM Team. HTM is a team that bears the name Hiroshi Fujiwara, Nike 'Air Jordan' and 'Air Max' design protagonist of Tinker Hatfield and Mark Parker, CEO of the initial design through to the Japanese street fashion loans. Which since 2002 it has designed more than 30 kinds of limited edition sneakers. CEO Parker had even the "Coby 11" series own design to commemorate the 2016 retirement of the long American professional basketball (NBA) player Kobe Bryant activities to the Nike brand models. CEO Parker will apply design principles to business. A "selection and concentration" through editing. He explained, "it is common that the design and management edit important" and "I put the key take away a bad thing, save a good thing." In an interview with one press. Representative examples I simplified the development of new business sectors. 2012 Nike research and development (R  D) team to review new product ideas that were reached in 350. CEO Parker proposed a priority basis, instead choosing to pursue an actual project directly and discuss it with the team. This Nike has developed singles focused on a major project 50. 2017 was nyeonen overhaul business abroad. Since 2009, first let's reduced earnings, reducing the number of stores has decided to concentrate on the major markets. Parker, CEO at the time cited the 12 cities of 10 countries, including Seoul, New York, London, Tokyo, Paris and Berlin as the main business. In these regions develop and produce products to meet local consumer tastes. Nike was expected that the share of these 12 cities occupied by revenue growth over the next year to reach 80%. Sales Channel was also massive Edit. Last October, the sales partners announced 30,000 julindago significantly from 40 pieces. Instead of strengthening the relationship with the remaining 40 partners and plans to advance the quality of the store. Also to identify trends and respond quickly regarded as an advantage of Parker's CEO. Since its inaugural Nike CEO is pushing many to a collaboration (Collaboration) project, along with other brands or celebrities. We launched in 1971 with nearly 50 years history of the Nike wihaeseoda still give the image that is leading the trend. Figure altogether leaving the design to the designer shoes of other brands. Since 2017 the past 12 years In off-white designer collaborative project were with popular brand of off-white until January Virgil ah blow to the reform of existing models such as the Air Jordan 1, Air Force 1, Nike Zoom Fly naenwatda a limited edition. It is active in utilizing new technologies. Nike is writing the movie, DreamWorks Animation company Nova a three-dimensional (3D) design of the system, in partnership with a subsidiary of Nova in product development. It utilizes a variety of operational data engineers gathered to look back up the sensor attached to the body. Two months choen acquired businesses Select Data. Big Data is a company built on local customers, product demand, helping to anticipate demand for logistics optimization. Last year, the company has also acquired the zodiac that analyzes consumer behavior and recommend customized products based on the user's Big Data. In marketing, sales and new attempts. Unlike other sneaker brand that rely on stars and early marketing leverage from a social network service (SNS). A way to purchase a limited edition ticket opportunity to apply only to those who share the limited edition release information on the SNS led to consumers to promote their own products. Limited Edition purchase rights was also assigned to the online lottery to raise the digital retailer. Nike has invested more than $ 1 billion only such apps (applications) and digital purchases this year. CEO Parker was expected to be a digital transactions proportion of more than 30% in total sales Nike until 2023.</string>
    <string name="cook">Picking a bachelor"s degree from Auburn University in 1960. Born in 1982, Industrial Engineering, and ttage a master"s degree from Duke University in 1988. After working in the Compaq 1998, Steve Jobs has called on Apple to come. At the time many people worked I was wondering this decision In Compaq Chief Operating Officer (COO) of the machine resale division and do and the people who worked 12 years in the North American general manager of IBM PC business suddenly almost transferred to net Hardy fucked Apple Why In a matter of course. Eventually over time his choice was a cut above God\'s Cook came to Apple it is cool to finally sewed CEO position. Of OM (Operations Management) areas above the performance of a brilliant career at Apple to support this assessment. Tim Cook was discarded by reducing the parts supply company was told the 100 to 20, and also abandoned lowers placed close to the production plant, and inventory existing on the 10th level at 70 days was saving huge costs, which guarantee high profits for Apple It became a springboard for. In 2007, this was due to rise above the 2-digit worldwide in SCM management and literacy. Since sticks the No. 1 position in the SCM management skills to the present day. Owing to this SCM reform to ensure the tremendous efficiency and cost savings it is Apple gave a great influence I got into a spot of now, promoted to Chief Operating Officer (COO) 2007 years. Heir class also secretly received were served as interim CEO when the organization in 2004, 2009, Steve Jobs sick nd, 2011 after Jobs died, Apple\'s CEO is to rise to the organization. At first, "Shall what is Apple without Steve Jobs?" While it expand its capabilities in the management aspects yeoteuna skeptical mood in the leadership of Cook without acceleration. If Jobs is innovation, etc. constitute the iPhone and iPad, Macbook laid the foundation of Apple, Tim Cook, is one who created a company with a dominant position Apple as excellent managerial skills. It has been achieved over the post-Jobs world\'s first company market capitalization, stock price also jumped nearly seven-fold after Jobs. Only the look of these indicators of the ability of the executive Tim Cook is no doubt. From the arbitrary nature, but nature is rather than Jobs, but also very tough guy and Jobs and Cook given rise to the load. I was famous to a very regular life, 3:00 am to get up 45 minutes the other countries who differential think not to call in, and we usually call the staff on Sunday evenings, etc. to think what to do next week … The many anecdotes and anecdotes are a little workaholic level. In one anecdotal report the person sitting in the meeting while the Chinese production plant, "Why Can still here?" China has never abandoned immediately sent a word. (…) popped torn down, but the money accumulated dividends to Apple, jeongjak and he himself received no dividends of $ 75 million. Foolish enough to get in at the time the worlds highest salary with more than $ 60 billion worth of money in the stock dividend is CEO does not look much. May 2013 stood at hearings to testify about the tax evasion allegations of Apple. While keeping a global leader in the market to the worldwide move to tax the income tax rate is lower refuge, but recent growth in the United States, because the money is jyeotgi punctuated the debate on if you do not come back to the United States. Cook in chapter hearing, testimony was that "Apple has done everything to the last penny tax to pay," deobuleoseo urged that "it is the US tax system needs to be realized." "We need to simplify the tax," even through the open column former CEO and current chairman Eric Schmidt of Google for topics such as #. # Beyond the statement of intent, in an interview with Bloomberg late last year. "We have our tax measures (tax evasion) is proud of" # of atmospheres have to speak even if legitimate tax strategy to go even damage the moral issues even as It seems unlikely. But I jeongjak hearing chapter atmosphere hwagiaeae, John McCain was tossed about a joke, saying, "Why should every day to update the app on my iPhone" to Tim Cook. # This is a realistic analysis of the crisis on the US manufacturing industry, which is reflected in the recent recession that crush on one of the worlds largest manufacturer Apple. Apple is a conciliatory gesture somehow Apple as last year, came to show the hagetdaneun motion before some Mac products being manufactured in China to the United States, in fact, sensitive US government to manufacturing jobs as from the beginning of the year the Mac Mini production made in the USA because there was a need to take bringing more jobs to the United States. As you can see in that giant Apple and Google chief Eric Schmidt Tim Cook and speak of a global company, they claimed that the bar is very consistent. Without the moral blame for the high level of relations 1. The tax that we will fully pay our taxes to pay all legitimate ways and 2. The need to lower the current reality of the unreal tax system and tax rates. Currently, tax, depending on the material of the company, but because reap tax depending on where you reform the tax system caused sales to taxation in accordance with the material of the customer can geoteul taxes more transparent and lowering the excess tax rate of the US foreign it is the gist of the claim is cash earned in the natchura barriers coming into the United States. The figures degrees button comes with Apple"s enterprise-scale business in this or that technique as been managed in the decade behind the scenes. In Apple's earnings announcement made on April Cook he was promised a dividend to shareholders, chose the method of issuing a corporate bond financing for them. This also moves the day Apple scale of corporate bonds issued by a whopping $ 17 billion in 30-year (divided into fine luggage). To listen to Apple's cash, which contains the so-called tax havens to sleep inside the United States, but charged a higher tax, a kind of tax books selected because you can raise capital at a much cheaper price than the issue corporate bonds. March 2014 to sell shares to some shareholders at the Annual General Meeting of Shareholders that was turned off by Apple. Cook was replaced the power supply in this facility many companies interested in renewable energy and environmental conservation as a significant amount of renewable energy, the company shareholders' perspective In this spirit me.Aren't good andago help shape thinking on profit. Some disgruntled shareholders would have raised, but the agenda is the promotion geumhara environmental policy was opposed by a number of shareholders Cook word. Jobs in principle (4 inch sticks Pen and Touch N) to be broke his choice. Of course, Jobs had said, "Now Make your Apple", was also listening to the story according to detractors competitors thanks. Once, when Steve Jobs is to pass the CEO directly to Cook it referred to the case of teachers, while the Walt Disney Company and the or caught in the past days to go in the right direction to such questions, do not do think for themselves and "Jobs How would ramen" sinsindangbu did. In other words, Cook is true (it's good or bad) is going to be the leader in the other direction and Jobs is one that has already been predicted. And it states that, because of its divergence are increasingly critical towards the cook. [Though Tim Cook is clearly psychic, but there are many types of feedback works as inspiration rather unfortunate lot spleen problems, such as Jobs. Plainly speaking, if more than Steve Jobs is full of dreams and visions who, Cook is a realist obsessed with profits to the bone. Inde Duke MBA in Riga just part not give lead the voting rights of the planning and strategy of major products brought into interlocking parts also with the management structure of Apple's distinctive deformed, once Jobs, Apple faced a crisis, Steve again, all to Jobs, including operating other parts should look as handsome as a councilor while trailing tteoneomgi. For those not familiar with the normal corporate brainwashing through to the end of the corporate philosophy and vision in our employees and continuing education, basically fit management philosophy does not even adopted. It was the post-Jobs noise will also be torn in management and product planning happens it is all Voting is focused on the position of CEO. One appointed Cook as CEO gun was a reasonable choice for the confidence of investors, will sit Heaney described below are things that happen to people who value efficiency, the CEO of Apple company to focus on vision. Once it has poor stability of the operating system. Update Support's a good day, often while Sudan upgrade bug manman change occurs and re-upgrade … Problems unprecedented in hardware - such as the iPhone and bent like a bow occurs. But for a time seemed right to look at La limits according to the characteristics of these enterprises is the same problem that Apple rather than the limitations of Tim Cook. Because by outsourcing all products it produced other than the operating system, software, design and development of key components such as iOS entrusted to a contractor because they affect the final product quality, production technology, according to the level of any of the partners. So it is supported heavily on partners such as foundry company Foxconn seeking to improve skills. But in December 2017 he pop the battery gate, simply technology is bujokhange as management ideas, and even became embroiled in criticism that there is a problem to the moral part of this problem kigo to the battery aging your own performance limits options in iOS 11.3 dwaetjiman been able pulls priority is resolved, it reduces performance by deliberately concealing haewatdaneun place without notice to the user for more than one year is evident. As well as getting more criticism found that knowing just released a fact that may be the iPhone 6 bend easily. See and subjected in 2017 it has received strong criticism against the goods deungbong in price and bundles of new products. IPhone X is too expensive can buy coffee myeotjan value ahkkimyeon criticism from consumers on earth to much old coffee yago remarks by were attracted wide aggro support fast charging, but jeongjak because Articles General Chargers that included high-speed filling a cup and 90,000 won worth out to buy a high-speed charger and cable. This policy has led to expensive iPhone in 2018 XR, iPhone XS, iPhone Xs Max starts at $ 749 USD each US dollar terms, $ 999, 1099 and, in the case of Xs Max 512GB model, amounting to 1,499 US dollars (!!!). In addition, the iPhone gives cash until 8 and X has not started to put the basic components Lightning port was -3.5 8 pie converts gender iPhone and even that newly produced (…) in addition to high-speed charger is still not put. Consumers "We believe that consumers are always there to purchase innovative technologies at an affordable price" True Worth it not true motivation seemed iPhone XS is no longer the price of the iPhone XS There the majority seemed a frosty response Tim Cook is about it until the iPhone XR and " Apple has a sufficient customer base to raise revenue, "he said openly. The "reading, learning, health, have the value you can not have imagined the iPhone is done by money management," I was explaining why the price of the iPhone expensive, I did not hear only an excuse naesewo despite not the Features of the iPhone only and two euros still believed to be. # Following the addition of last year, the value of coffee drip time is being pulled aggro that you can buy one US dollar a day, the iPhone faces XS Max out also that the extremists to cut timkuk at home and abroad. People who love Apple and see why critics continue to make useless remarks scratching the rash nyamyeo. As a result, the look and the iPhone, released in 2018 jungeseon dont XR cheaper iPhone is the best selling well, there are many reactions that jonbeo already released devices. Eventually from 2018 and does not disclose sales of the iPhone. Adds share price was believed to slowdown in sales and US market even without sintongchi in the Chinese market exceeded $ 200 per week in the fall of 2018 has plummeted to $ 150 in January 2019. At one time when you've had enough to slope downward to the Nasdaq, Apple to negative. Of course, it stands hollering than to have perished Apple iPhone slump in 2018 but the case is that Tim Cook just put on a long-term seolrebal continues to push a lot of expensive policies is still debate on whether to get any results. After all was indirectly admitted by the fact that expensive policy failure on January 29, 2019 decided to cut chulgoga in some areas. Also in 2020 launched the second generation of SE connects the existence of a low-end iPhone in the iPhone SE launched in 2016. However, some parts are still turning a chogoga policies of some of the line-up in external demand, the reason that consumers are still criticized mental noticed less. The WWDC 2019 is raising doubts about the continued high price policy in placing the 999 US dollars-old monitor stand the laughingstock of the world. Of course, the iPod, but suffer always compared with Jobs in that it did not come out this product to seek a breakthrough convenience and innovation like the iPhone, that this term while Apple Watch and Air Pot products to users technology and ease of use enhancements such as Tim Cook simplicity came out this innovative gone to the post-Jobs Apple has it that this new invention eopeotdago crowd.</string>
    <string name="waren">A master of value investing approach to investment at a lower price than the company\'s value. To see a list of one person investment company Berkshire Hathaway document. Danta and well and still be there if ever able to fund only the minimum rate of return of 50% per year. Investments greatest investment. Nebraska in Omaha former nickname Sage of Omaha (Oracle of Omaha). Living life in the United States, Nebraska, Omaha City put these two aliases. Buffett and a few neighbors who lived in the same neighborhood were never invest money when Buffett was a child. Of course, many were hit. A pediatrician named Carol Angel believes malman Buffett invested in 1957 was $ 10,000 and neuleonatdago 69 million to $ 400 million in 2008. Be a good neighbor once I hit the case. According to Jie \"Forbes\" in October 2008 based on his property was occupied first place in the world at about $ 58 billion, it was ranked third with 47 billion US dollars in 2010. In September 2008 the global financial crisis, when the price seems to be a lot of it down strike. Current chairman Jeff Bezos in 2019, Bill Gates, the world\'s fourth Bernardo Following ranks the Arno president. There is often mentioned as an example of the importance of long-term investments and benefits, from 1965 to 2014 was geodwot revenue CAGR of 21.6%, which amounted to 1,826,163 percent. Indeed welfare terminator. And more than 99% of the property that acquired after the age of 50. Annual rate of return itself is rather increased explosively, but the amount dropped since the Middle Ages. Of course, Buffett\'s investment tube is not explained only long-term investment. Investment pipe paragraph reference. But it can be thought of as people who have lived a life without regret, and that its own viscosity regrets in life. One of them is that when you start from the age of 11 stocks. If you want to be born again, starting at the age of five or seven years old. When viewed from the point of regret that should have been the stock from the age of five seems to be the importance of time is limited, you know exactly than anyone. Buffett was a stockbroker youth was born as the son of Howard Buffett Homann, former Republican congressman. After graduate school was also briefly worked at a securities company that operates father. But soon learned the technique from the investments, \"Graham Newman\" Graham is a professional investment company. So even when I give a talk about his childhood, the story makes a lot of anecdotes about Alba he had money when I was young buck than family story. For example, any ttaera was a matter ttaera Boy Restaurants bus was a grocery store clerk makes a lot of talking like that. When six-year-old sold chewing gum and coke. See the chart when buying a 11-year-Cities Service preferred stock investment began. I bought 38 shares of Cities Service sold dollars at around $ 40 and they felt the importance of long-term investment groups exceeded $ 200 later. 12 is a saljjeum shop moved to Washington. Let\'s say the teacher has ATandT short selling a ATandT (!) Boyeojwoseo one of his trading statement was an insult jugido psychological pressure. I bought a 49,000 pyeong of farmland north Omaha when I was 15 years old. When 17-year-old began the pinball machine rental business. It had already written a number of monthly income than his school teachers in the late teens. From elementary school when it has obtained a waiver for early assignment qualifications than motivation. But there was no thought want to go to college. Because he considered himself a member of society yirwot groups are already economically successful investment and business college he thought was a waste of time. Then there was the heart of the university are below the level considered teaching yourself. But eventually the father is encouraged to college. The original University of Pennsylvania Wharton School of Economics at the actor two years, had earned a bachelor\'s in early after graduation moved to the University of Nebraska, obtaining a Master of Economics at the Columbia University Graduate School of Business. After graduating from the University of Nebraska undergraduate he fell to ruin a job interview, but support for the Harvard University Graduate School of Business. All professors of Harvard has an anecdote that \"you are too young hagieneun support to Harvard.\" In a time it delayed anecdotes while he was disappointed. According to his biography (snowball) Buffett is his friend said, \"I think the Harvard name value, that is, the sign over, Tom. I think that Harvard did not fit me want yirang Talent. Ought to reflect,\" he said. I started to find away back then graduate to Harvard, then it is the Columbia Business School found. This is itdeora and David Dodd, Professor Ben Graham teachers teach, and I thought that he was not two minutes Overlooking the world deseo such Olympian, if I, if the entrance is really nice. There meets Benjamin Graham. Graham is a character had a great impact on Buffett with Philip Fisher. I Wallaby \"15% to Fischer, 85% had an impact on Graham,\" he should. If you have the time, he would not just pass the Harvard today. Among publications related to the equity investment it is to exceed that of the Fisher and Graham did not yet found. Buffett\'s millionaire ranks already heard the 35-year-old has bought Berkshire. Protege Partners hedge fund managers in 2007 and over the next decade and the return of Protege Partners SandP500 index fund will be higher for the return of any of the five hedge funds that had bet even the 320,000 US dollars each bet. Who wins the pot is going to donate to charity. Buffett\'s investment professionals are expected to win. However, there are opinions that Protege Partners actually win because of Protege Partners geodwot a great advertising effect only to the 320,000 US dollars using the Buffett. Late 2017 SandP500 based index fund Buffett chose had recorded an average annual return of 7.1% in hedge funds Protege Partners are selected record yield of 2.1% was a bet Warren Buffett victory. Buffett was cold in 2007, he said that investing in stocks of over 20 companies from South Korea specifically stated haeteotdago hold Kia Motors, Shinyoung Securities, Hyundai Steel, KTandG, for milling, of POSCO shares. However, POSCO was nawatdago robbing all the shares in the 2010\'s, and with good reason been found in recent years. Samsung Securities Co., ghosts situation. See POSCO. 2018 Today just seemed a little fold Korea stock market investment themselves. South Korea has disposed of most of the company\'s total amount of shares. In fact, the public disclosure by Berkshire Hathaway shareholder to hold more than 5% of company shares is not even a single one in 2018. Even in 2008 the sub-prime mortgage crisis teojyeoteul Buffett became the majority shareholder of Goldman Sachs had quietly survived a love call. Conversely, in the process of collapse of Bear Stearns raised launched the flare of the financial crisis, Bear Stearns and haeteotdago matter please dont get investment for Buffett. Therefore, Buffett would answer their executive under the condition that the investment in Bear Stearns investment but also management refused him. Buffett was aware of the fact that it does not also invest executives because there is a terrible problem with Bear Stearns, and did not even own investments. Pot was 640,000 US dollars is invested in government bonds and Berkshire Hathaway B shares and that about 2 million US dollars as of late 2017. The money charities Girls Inc. of Nebraska It will be donated to the of Omaha. Prostate cancer in 2012, one group received the decision. Prostate cancer is a cancer that gotjal disease from older men. In 2013 he joined Twitter. And that the contribution to the Fortune If you wish to join a lot of people may encounter. Warren Buffett were many interested in value stocks to exert dominance on the market in 2013 was jointly acquired the food company Heinz with Brazilian private equity fund 3G Capital scale to create a giant food company called Heinz Kraft merged with Kraft followed by a two-year investment had a faded look lost on a large scale. There Berkshire Hathaway has a 26.7 percent stake in Kraft Heinz, Heinz Kraft will neomgyeotdeon 140 billion in 2019 happened a tragedy favorite jjogeura with earnings of 87 million dollars. May reflect that \"like Kraft sangeot too expensive.\" With only 40 years in 2020 it said it has agreed to sell 31 newspapers in the United States Publisher Lee Enterprise Corona 19 pandemics in 2020 the economy saw a number of investment gurus are damaged due to the price crash in 2020 that happened was I seriously damage . Buffett was no exception, but is not, is too expensive, while the US stock market has had a majority of 150 trillion of assets in cash, a winner of going or combed in days of bombings Corona contain literally wipe out the last remaining. As well as hundreds of one hundred million won about the same, but have also put out snacks rain a few hundred units to one hundred million won Buffett\'s company with leading assets and labor world-class nuclear bombs shocked the stock right of the aviation industry. However, starting from mid-March 2020 was a major US Nasdaq Composite Stock Price Index and the Dow starts, including V purpura is within NASDAQ Point 30 June 2020 was to achieve 10,000 points. Nevertheless, they make a donation. Natural gas transportation and storage of energy sector assets of Dominion (Dominion Energy) in July was to buy 40 billion (4.8 trillion won). Berkshire Hathaway Inc. holding back shares in August. Synonymous with value investing is the most famous value investors in the world. Corporate Buffett looking for: 1) to understand the business and the (circle of competence), 2) good long-term economics to predict (or 510 years back, and), and 3) an incredible management team and (management), 4) acquisition price this is a reasonable (margin of safety) companies. In Buffett\'s perspective that growth, such as IT companies And then often treated as a hero of the innovations I 1), 2) and 4) all failed yiraseo tend rather reluctant. Buffett\'s mentor was Benjamin Graham is considered important to buy undervalued stocks. Buffett is known that this is important to buy good companies when further stocks are undervalued. Warren Buffett is the original bar is thorough but prefer the way Benjamin Graham\'s investment approach, using the experience acquired in 1972 Siege candy three times the book value stated in the beginning and made the current investment philosophy. Warren Buffett is 80% of his investment scheme Graham, Philip Fisher has said 20% of La. Buffett If you directly write a book about how their investment is not only once. But they would often comment on their investment Pavilion at the annual shareholder meeting of Berkshire Hathaway, and letters and CNBC, Forbes. Eopnya idea to write a book and tell me to have questions, refer to the Annual General Meeting of Shareholders on the letter or because their investments have already told the pipe at a general shareholders\' meeting of Berkshire Hathaway. But the author is directly involved through the years of the book there is a book of interviews That\'s called \"snowball (Snowball)\". We ask Alice Schroeder was Wall Street analysts have written their own electricity, see Schroeder interviews and other materials is a book written for five years. Thus, although not directly involved authored dont book snowball only one remaining is the book came up with a third party creation. MMF, deposits such investments are known to be safe but I think in practice risky assets. When an article claiming to increase the share of deposits in safe assets in the media, on the contrary, Buffett is considered that the number of shares. Do not think about gold is known as a good investment destination. When the investment in the history of gold was popular rather than a higher return on what to buy stocks. Only a small portion of gold demand, gold teeth, spent on IT products, more than 90% of said ornamental inde simply not to invest in a gold ornamental counterproductive. About oil investment is known as negative. Buffett has said no to that idea would be to say that its investment makes sense, because gold, oil, paintings, etc. would have to be the price determined by the valuation of other investors. I think companies that are undervalued relative to the US companies are tons to South Korea, but the market capitalization and trading volume should tteoleojindago write down the investment attractiveness. If you search the Internet, yet only country in the world with a system that can see all the information about the company is free to praise the DART system, saying only South Korea. Information about the DART system is carried on almost every year it sent letters to shareholders ahead of the Berkshire Hathaway shareholders \'meeting (corresponding to Chapter attended the shareholders\' meeting in Korea). The privately held company is not actually listed companies in the United States is no disclosure system itself. DART also of Korea shall be the basic financial statements unlisted companies. For real estate investments such as single-family homes unexpectedly farmland and is known as positive. Also assets that can respond to inflation, and real estate is because yeogigi called productive investment. SNS companies pointed out that the highly overvalued. Credit rating of the United States is said to be not a AAA AAAA (actually not rated). Buffett has shown boundless confidence for the United States. Berkshire Hathaway is also reserves all the sseundago to buy US Treasury bonds. Buffett lot of people only know how to long positions in stocks that profit actually produce a profit in many ways like a return of the financial investment. Buffett will participate in the CDS, bonds, foreign exchange, commodities, indices, individual stocks, mainly to short positions in the futures and options markets. But like George Soros, rather than trying to analyze a lot of money because of the purpose of hedging. In fact, the financial position of Berkshire Hathaway, the ratio of short positions held by Berkshire has managed not to exceed 25% of equity assets, compared with a long position. With the highest 23% when 20,072,008 years at the time of the global financial crisis and then after the shiny edge is 15%. Top-down approach when investing (→ Economic Enterprises) than it naerindago the decision after analyzing a bottom-up approach (→ Economic Enterprises). However, Buffett noted that the chance of a bottom-up approach because the US is also growing macroeconomic always came when applicable. That companies generate revenue in any way and do not invest if they fail to understand. Investment in IBM is claiming to be jyeotgi simple so IBM can understand this yourself. And that only invest in companies with economic moats (Economic moat). And that entry barriers (monopoly, oligopoly), brands, patents, economies of scale, etc. do not lose him it would be the most important investment principle is an important principle for the second does not forget the principles of the sector. Airlines have had no intention of investments. The former is invested in US Airways is why it is also damaging to his name, and that growth is uncertain due to excessive fixed costs and competition. Private rental plane will be there to hold firm NetJets. But it said that in the 2017 General Meeting of Shareholders invest a total of $ 100 billion in the United States four carriers. Due to Corona of 19 Then the aviation industry is a direct hit for doeja April May also sell its shares in Delta Airlines, as well 5 January 2020 2020 \"has sold a total amount of aviation stocks,\" he said at the shareholders\' meeting. Like a buffet to admit their mistakes quickly, \"No regret to quickly pull out the money that US $ 70 to 8,000,000,000, which was my mistake,\" he said. Buffett think the casino business would continue to grow as long as human civilization exists. But always there is no plan to invest itgie facing the possibility of legal regulations but is morally wrong. Also take the risk described above is a large enough company to invest in addition to the casino business, and that it will not invest in a casino business. What a turnaround companies or start-up losses were not became established turned into a surplus in recent years, and no interest. The ROE prefer a steady nopeumyeonseo company. Buffett itgie investing in a number of businesses, applying the crystallization of the equity investment department expressions diversified portfolio? The assessment can be called. But as Buffett mentioned nucha His portfolio includes Coca-Cola, Wells Fargo companies like Costco and the majority of the share, and the share of companies such as The Washington Post, Moodyz hapchyeodo does not exceed 10%. But Buffett has said that not concentrating investments suitable to the general individual investors. Most of the general individual investors the ability to select an item lacking were 90%, 10% in US short-term government bonds to prop the cost of living and the bear market in index funds that track a person in the US stock market representative index SandP500 than invested in several companies it is recommended that the best investment if you want to invest in a private company said that a portfolio with many events as possible. The Company expects lower yields than long-term government bond should never pardon. If the stock market is likely to lower expected returns than long-term government bonds to sell the shares and increase the share of government bonds in the portfolio. Fortunately, the stock market has recorded a higher expected return than long-term government bonds during most of the period. But Buffett is instructive that have already experienced many times when I do not know the bear market will be bearish again when it comes. He considers that they can record higher returns than large-cap stocks are small caps. However, unlike the initial Now is ahswipdago failed to invest in small caps to the working capital fund is too large. The reason for while buying the company\'s shares delisted and bought all of the shares (100%) Dividends (GEICO, BNSF (Burlington Northern Santa Fe), etc.), a 100% subsidiary of the shares will be exempt from the existing dividend tax. (It is already subsidiary is because dividend after paying the income tax, and I bite the income tax on dividends if there is ikgeum non inclusion system because its double taxation in the United States and developed countries are exempt from dividend tax in accordance with the percentage of jibunryul and the entire proceeds and) makes more I know, the minute the wind OK. To stop the takeover interference from other shareholders (especially dividend portion) is famous because it has absolute faith in the United States on their investments. For example, make sure that the aftermath of the global financial crisis was the most powerful to October, the investment community and private investors fell in disappointment in 2008, the number of \"US stocks. I would have these articles are titled accident \"pulled the effect that the writer of the New York Times to restore investor confidence actually makes a little drop, people really bought US stocks according to him 10 years later jackpot. Since October 2008, ten years alone SandP500 index expanded more than 400% is due. As well as copies were brought to the tune of $ 340 billion BNSF Railway Company of America 2 above during 09 years, it was worth a lot of money at that time 25% of the assets held by Berkshire Hathaway. Many people think that the financial crisis puts that money to put a traditional military industrial railway company neither new growth sectors were criticized and \"The Buffett was finally senile knots.\" However, Buffett did say the reason to buy the company in a word, \"I believe the US economy to be revived.\" He said showed faith in the development of the United States once again. He was \"America will overcome this crisis again, resume and logistics industry will move again. Then the railway company will grow back,\" say, was actually so. BNSF\'s operating profit increased from $ 1.8 billion in 2009 to $ 5.0 billion after 10 years, will pay dividends to the parent company, Berkshire $ 300 million over 10 years was almost recovered purchase price only dividends. Warren Buffett\'s bet on the revival of the US economy will hit enter again. In addition, Buffett has continued to export signal that the enormous liquidity that they may have to spend the US economy overcome the crisis. 08 years financial crisis, \"my desk phone is always open,\" he means, if a company experiencing a crisis at any time, a call was received that advice and assistance for their investment. Which together effective in 2020, and his comrades Charlie Ruff hanging from the April 2020 interview, \"the Economic so difficult Buffett\'s phone does not ring,\" he said, \"it seems so unthinkable ask for help Buffett never be the economy hard.\" there bars. However this does not help anybody businesses that the crisis does, in fact, but asking for help call to the September 2008 Lehman Brothers, Buffett refused to give the Buffett analysis of the company help the bankrupt Lehman Brothers after a few days. Conversely, other banks Goldman Sachs and Bank of America has been greatly contribute to actually revive the bank to invest $ 50 billion each store has also achieved a significant profit. Faith in Buffett in the US together also valid for the current 2020 eotdeutyi pull the United States to overcome the various crises, including in the Berkshire Hathaway shareholders\' meeting held on May 2nd 2020 \"The Great Depression, World War II, 911, terrorism, the global financial crisis this 19 in corona situation I believe the American Magic and think about the future of the US economy positively, \"he said. Also shows several indicators of the past economic crisis, the United States, including the Great Depression. \"The United States has always been richer and develop a more healthy direction. Therefore, I want to say is just do not say never bet on the US opposition.\" Innovation was once again recommended that long-term investments in US stocks. If I believe in the power of the United States to invest in the long term, the US ETF market and will be able to earn higher profits than any other financial product</string>
</resources>